Jane: Hello. My name’s Jane.
Expert: Hi, Jane. So, why are you calling?
Jane: Well, a month ago, my friend Susan and I decided to go on holiday together
this summer, to Italy.
So we planned everything and, er, I was really looking forward to it,
as Susan’s an old friend and I don’t see her very often.
But the other day, she told me that she was telling another friend of hers about our holiday –
somebody I don’t know, a woman called Angie – and Angie was really interested,
and now Susan has invited her to come, too.
Susan never asked me what I thought! I don’t even know Angie,
and I really don’t want to go on holiday with someone I don’t know.
What should I do?